[Music]
In today's video, we're going to talk
about Fino Payment Bank. In
today's video, I'll
tell you how to get a Fino Payment Bank retailer ID.
What documents are required to get a Fino Payment Bank retailer ID?
What is the process through which you
can get an ID in a very short time? And what is the cost of getting the ID?
I'll also tell you
what services you get after getting a Fino Retailer ID and password,
which you can refer to your customers.
How much commission can you share by using all those services?
And then, if you
also want to get a Fino Premika Distributor ID,
how can you get it? I'm going to
give complete information through today's video. So, let's find out
[Music]
how you can get a retailer ID for these three payment banks. Before that, let's first find out
what services you get after getting an Fino Payment Bank retailer ID,
which you can offer to your customers.
[Music]
If we talk about print services,
you can see that you do
n't get DMT.  You get the service of domestic money transfer,
you get the
service of international money transfer from here,
you can open an account here, in which
you can open two or three Prakash accounts on your own, there is
also an account through Pragati,
first savings account and simple
savings and in this way many accounts are available
which you can open, along with this you get the
service of ABS, you get the service of Aadhar Enabled Payment
System, you can
withdraw money from Aadhar card, you
can make deposits and
you get the service of POS for front add point,
even bill payment service is available here, you
can pay any bill from here, if you want to pay
chapel water bill,
electricity bill, you can send
an email, history of table, if you want to
recharge TV,
you can use all these bills, after this you can
recharge your mobile, you can recharge it,
you can see through this process,
you get the gas management system, you
can manage it,
related to travel, you can book tickets from here, in
which you can see that you can
book railway tickets, book train tickets  You
can book air tickets
and hotel tickets from here, you
get all these services which you can offer
to your customers by taking the retailer ID of Fino Payment Bank
and after this we will know
how much commission you can earn by using all these services.
[Music]
You can come to check the Fino Payment Bank commission chart here, you can see it
here,
like partner.fino.fino.paymentbank.whatsapp. Friends, you will
come from here and will come to its official website, you can see it from here,
I will give you its link
in the description box of this video, you can
click from there and go
below, you can see it from here, you will be told about the offers, which you can see from here, I
told you that from here
friends, your commission chart is Micro
ATM Special Offer,
you can see about all the offers from here and if you
want more detailed information about the offers, in
which I have made a particular video and
uploaded it on the channel, I will give the link in
both the description box and office eye button of this video,
you
can go there and watch the video and then the message will be about you.  You
can get complete information
like you can see here, you can see it
on the micro ATM form if you want to see it, you
can see it in the gym, if the
maximum has been mentioned, you
can use the maximum leaves, which have been
told that from here you can see that
between Rs. 7000 to 10,000, friends, you
can help on commission, similarly, you can
make videos about all the offer typing and
watch the video, now after this let
us know how you can get its ID,
if we talk about the retailer ID of your frame,
its cost will be 199, you
can get its repair ID from here for 199 rupees
and how to get it, then you have to
contact this number, but
before getting the ID, one thing you have to keep in mind is
that you should have these three things, that
you can see, you should have this PAN
card, Aadhar card
and fingerprint device, if
you have all these things then also you can
call on the given number, from here you  You can get an ID
if you don't have these three things,
first for all three things, after that you
call from here, you will get that
friend, if you want to get its distributor ID,
you can see such distributor ID
cost will be Rs.10000,
you can get distributor ID of Hindi films
for ten thousand rupees, now
this number has been given for how to get the ID, you can contact on this number
8083, you can contact on this number,
friends, you will get the distributor ID, if you are
fortunate enough, then the complete process which
I told about Pinup Amrit, let me tell you
how you can get the ID, I liked this video of the commission a
lot, I liked the video,
like the video, do video conferences,
apart from this, if you have any doubt in your mind,
then
definitely tell us by commenting in the comment box of this video, if you
can add them directly to this program, I will
also try my best to reply to you,
follow me and
you can ask any question in your mind in this program as
well, you will get the link of Telegram,
you must definitely
do Amazon because all the  New updates,
commission chart, whenever any update comes, I
share it with you from time to time on Telegram,
so you must go there and follow and come
on my channel for the first time, till now you have
subscribed, subscribe to the channel,
click on the call for the bell icon,
whatever updates in this useful video,
its notification will
reach you first, on this side Pinjre
Institute, till then Jai Hind Take
Care